pulse2.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy governs pulse2.com, a website owned by Pulse 2.0 LLC. At Pulse 2.0, we fully understand the importance of your privacy and we strive to respect your privacy.

## **SUMMARY**

Pulse 2.0 may collect certain non-personally identify information about you as you use our website (pulse2.com). We may use this data to better understand our users. We may also ask you to provide certain personal information, but you’ll always be able to opt out. If you give us personal information, we promise to fully respect your privacy. It is Pulse 2.0 LLC’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## **HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION  **

Like most website operators, Pulse 2.0 collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Pulse 2.0’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use its website.

Pulse 2.0 also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Pulse 2.0 does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. We may also collect and use IP addresses to block users who violated our Terms of Service.

Certain visitors to Pulse 2.0 choose to interact with Pulse 2.0 in ways that require Pulse 2.0 to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Pulse 2.0 gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Pulse 2.0 collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Pulse 2.0. For example, if you provide us with your email address to sign up for our newsletter, we will only use your email address to send you our newsletter. Pulse 2.0 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Service-related activities on Pulse 2.0.

Additionally, some interactions, such as posting a comment, may ask for personal information. For instance, when posting a comment, may provide a website that will be displayed along with a user’s name when the comment is displayed. Supplying such personal information is completely optional and is only displayed for the benefit and the convenience of the user.

## **LOG DATA & ANALYTICS**

Pulse 2.0 may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to the Service. For instance, Pulse 2.0 may monitor the most popular parts of the pulse2.com. Pulse 2.0 may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Pulse 2.0 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Pulse 2.0 uses third party analytics services to measure traffic to our website. The third party analytics services collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our site. This may include information such as your browser type, browser version, the pages of our site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. Pulse 2.0 does not collect any personally identifiable information through the use of our analytics services.

## **HOW WE USE INFORMATION**

Pulse 2.0 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to provide services available at Pulse 2.0’s websites, and that have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Pulse 2.0 will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Pulse 2.0 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Pulse 2.0 believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Pulse 2.0, third parties or the public at large.

## **COOKIES**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the Service each time the visitor returns. Pulse 2.0 uses cookies to help Pulse 2.0 identify and track visitors, their usage of Pulse 2.0 Service, and their Service access preferences. Pulse 2.0 visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Pulse 2.0’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Pulse 2.0’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## **DATA STORAGE**

Pulse 2.0 uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Service. You understand that although you retain full rights to your data, it may be stored on third party storage and transmitted through third party networks.

## **PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Pulse 2.0 may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Pulse 2.0’s sole discretion. Pulse 2.0 encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
